Guide to the Central Washington University Athletics Department, Team Sports Collection 1923-2007 (bulk 1965-1995)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Scrapbooks, XI
  - CWU Women's Basketball stats, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 95-6)
  - CWU Women's Basketball stats, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 95-7)
  - CWU Women's Basketball Career Stats, 1984-1992 (Box-folder 95-8)
  - CWU Women'sbasketball hoop camp, 1989 (Box-folder 95-9)
  - CWU Women's Basketball Stats, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 95-10)
  - CWU Women's Basketball, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 95-11)
  - CWU Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 95-12)
  - CWU Women's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 95-13)
  - CWU Women's basketball stats, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 95-14)
  - CWU Women's basketball stats, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 95-15)
  - CWU Athletics Stats (Box-folder 95-16)
  - CWU Men's Track and Field stats, 1923-1995 (Box-folder 96-1)
  - CWU Men's Track and Field stats, 1955-1977 (Box-folder 96-2)
  - CWU Men's Track and Field stats, 1971-1981 (Box-folder 96-3)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 96-4)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 96-5)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 96-6)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 96-7)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1989-1991 (Box-folder 96-8)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 96-9)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 96-10)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1997 (Box-folder 96-11)
  - CWU Men's Track and Field stats, 1998 (Box-folder 96-12)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 1999 (Box-folder 96-13)
  - CWU Men's Track and Field stats, 2000 (Box-folder 96-14)
  - CWU Men's Cross Country Stats, 2000 (Box-folder 96-15)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1965-1973 (Box-folder 97-1)
  - CWU Women's track results, 1967-1982 (Box-folder 97-2)
  - CWU Women's Track stats, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 97-3)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1976 (Box-folder 97-4)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1977 (Box-folder 97-5)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1978 (Box-folder 97-6)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1979 (Box-folder 97-7)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1980 (Box-folder 97-8)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1981 (Box-folder 97-9)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1982 (Box-folder 97-10)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1983 (Box-folder 97-11)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1985 (Box-folder 97-12)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1987 (Box-folder 97-13)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1989 (Box-folder 97-14)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1990 (Box-folder 97-15)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1992 (Box-folder 97-16)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1993 (Box-folder 97-17)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1994 (Box-folder 97-18)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1995 (Box-folder 97-19)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 97-20)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1997 (Box-folder 97-21)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 1999 (Box-folder 97-22)
  - CWU Women's Track and field stats, 2000 (Box-folder 97-23)
  - CWU Women's Cross country stats, 2002 (Box-folder 97-24)
  - CWU Baseball win-loss records, 1927-1985 (Box-folder 98-1)
  - CWU Baseball rosters, 1927-1998 (Box-folder 98-2)
  - CWU Baseball year by year stats, 1927-1989 (Box-folder 98-3)
  - CWU Baseball all conference team information, 1954-1975 (Box-folder 98-4)
  - CWU career baseball stats, 1964-2000 (Box-folder 98-5)
  - CWU Baseball career pitching stats, 1964-2000 (Box-folder 98-6)
  - CWU Baseball evergreen conference stats, 1965-1974 (Box-folder 98-7)
  - CWU Misc records, 1967 (Box-folder 98-8)
  - CWU Baseball NAIA cahmpionships, 1968 (Box-folder 98-9)
  - CWU Baseball batting and fielding stats, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 98-10)
  - CWU Baseball stats, 1976 (Box-folder 98-11)
  - CWU Baseball scores, 1977 (Box-folder 98-12)
  - CWU Baseball wrap up, 1983 (Box-folder 98-13)
  - Evergreen Conference Baseball stats, 1985 (Box-folder 98-14)
  - CWU Baseball-NAIA world series, 1988 (Box-folder 98-15)
  - CWU Baseball Year by year stats, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 98-16)
  - CWU Baseball Stats, 1996 (Box-folder 98-17)
  - CWU Baseball Stats, 1997 (Box-folder 98-18)
  - CWU Baseball stats, 1998 (Box-folder 98-19)
  - CWU baseball stats, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 98-20)
  - CWU Baseball dinner fundraiser, 2012 (Box-folder 98-21)
  - CWU Baseball box scores, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 99-1)
  - CWU Baseball boxscores, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 99-2)
  - CWU Baseball box scores, 1992-1999 (Box-folder 99-3)
  - CWU Baseball boxscores, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 99-4)
  - CWU Baseball boxscores, 1996 (Box-folder 99-5)
  - CWU Men's swimming stats, 1959-1989 (Box-folder 100-1)
  - CWU Men's swimming Misc. Roster, 1966-1980 (Box-folder 100-2)
  - NAIA Swimming, 1975 (Box-folder 100-3)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1981-1985 (Box-folder 100-4)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 100-5)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 100-6)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 100-7)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 100-8)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 100-9)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 100-10)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 100-11)
  - CWU Men's swimming, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 100-12)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1974-1994 (Box-folder 100-13)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 100-14)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 100-15)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 100-16)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 100-17)
  - CWU Women's swimming, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 100-18)
  - CWU Wrestling Award winners, 1960-1999 (Box-folder 101-1)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1962-2000 (Box-folder 101-2)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 101-3)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1981-1990 (Box-folder 101-4)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 101-5)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 101-6)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 101-7)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 101-8)
  - CWU Wrestling stats, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 101-9)
  - CWU Men's Soccer Stats, 1965-1993 (Box-folder 102-1)
  - CWU soccer clippings, 1974-1980 (Box-folder 102-2)
  - CWU Men's soccer stats, 1981 (Box-folder 102-3)
  - CWU soccer Men and women's release, 1982 (Box-folder 102-4)
  - CWU Soccer Game stats, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 102-5)
  - NW Collegiate soccer conference, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 102-6)
  - CWU soccer Career stats, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 102-7)
  - CWU Men's soccer stats, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 102-8)
  - CWU Men's soccer release, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 102-9)
  - CWU Men's soccer game stats, 1989-1990 (Box-folder 102-10)
  - CWU Men's Soccer game stats, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 102-11)
  - CWU Game stats, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 102-12)
  - CWU Men's Soccer Stats, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 102-13)
  - CWU Game stats, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 102-14)
  - CWU Men's soccer box scores, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 102-15)
  - CWU Women's Soccer Stats, 1981-1989 (Box-folder 102-16)
  - NW collegiate soccer conference, 1983-1993 (Box-folder 102-17)
  - CWU Soccer General news, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 102-18)
  - CWU Women's soccer Stats, 1987-1992 (Box-folder 102-19)
  - CWU Women's Soccer Stats, 1987-2002 (Box-folder 102-20)
  - CWU Women's soccer game stats, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 102-21)
  - CWU Women's soccer Career stats, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 102-22)
  - CWU Women's Soccer Stats, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 102-23)
  - CWU Women's soccer releases, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 102-24)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 1994 (Box-folder 102-25)
  - CWU Soccer stats and updates, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 102-26)
  - CWU Women's soccer news release, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 102-27)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 1997 (Box-folder 102-28)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 102-29)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 102-30)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 2000 (Box-folder 102-31)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 2001 (Box-folder 102-32)
  - CWU Women's soccer stats, 2002-2003 (Box-folder 102-33)
  - CWU Tennis stats, 1980-1995 (Box-folder 103-1-1)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1980-1999 (Box-folder 104-1)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 104-2)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1996 (Box-folder 104-3)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 104-4)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1997 (Box-folder 104-5)
  - CWU news release volleyball, 1998 (Box-folder 104-6)
  - CWU volleyball stats, 1999 (Box-folder 104-7)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 104-8)
  - CWU Volleyball stats, 2001 (Box-folder 104-9)
  - CWU volleyball invitational, 2009 (Box-folder 104-10)
  - CWU Softball stats, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 105-1)
  - CWU Women's softball stats, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 105-2)
  - CWU Women's softball stats, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 105-3)
  - CWU Women's softball stats, 1997 (Box-folder 105-4)
  - CWU Women's softball stats, 1999 (Box-folder 105-5)
  - CWU Women's softball stats, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 105-6)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Wrestling, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-1)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Cross country, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 106-2)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Soccer, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-3)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Volleyball, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-4)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Women's basketball, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-5)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Tennis, 1993 (Box-folder 106-6)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU track and Field, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-7)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU softball, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-8)
  - newspaper clippings CWU all sports, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 106-9)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU swimming, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-10)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU Baseball, 1992-2006 (Box-folder 106-11)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU men's basketball, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 106-12)
  - Newspaper clippings CWU basketball, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 106-13)
  - newspaper clippings CWU football, 2003 (Box-folder 106-14)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1904-1907 (Box-folder 107-1)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1929-1930 (Box-folder 107-2)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1931-1932 (Box-folder 107-3)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 107-4)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 107-5)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1943-1946 (Box-folder 107-6)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1947-1949 (Box-folder 107-7)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1949 (Box-folder 107-8)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 107-9)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 107-10)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 107-11)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1954-1956 (Box-folder 107-12)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1955 (Box-folder 107-13)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1957 (Box-folder 107-14)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 107-15)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 107-16)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 107-17)
  - CWU basketball action shots, 1962 (Box-folder 107-18)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1963 (Box-folder 107-19)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1964 (Box-folder 107-20)
  - Dean Nicholson 1st season, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 107-21)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 107-22)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1966 (Box-folder 107-23)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 107-24)
  - CWU basketball action shots, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 107-25)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 107-26)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 107-27)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 107-28)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 107-29)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 107-30)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 107-31)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 107-32)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1985 (Box-folder 107-33)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1986 (Box-folder 107-34)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1987 (Box-folder 107-35)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1987-1989 (Box-folder 107-36)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 107-37)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1992 (Box-folder 107-38)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 107-39)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1996 (Box-folder 107-40)
  - CWU Basketball team photos, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 107-41)
  - CWU Basketball team photos (Box-folder 107-42)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1902-1904 (Box-folder 108-1)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 108-2)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1967 (Box-folder 108-3)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 108-4)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1984 (Box-folder 108-5)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 108-6)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 108-7)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 108-8)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 108-9)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1989-1999 (Box-folder 108-10)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 108-11)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 108-12)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 108-13)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 108-14)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 108-15)
  - CWU women's basketball action shots, 1980 (Box-folder 108-16)
  - CWU women's basketball action shots, 1990-2000 (Box-folder 108-17)
  - CWU women's basketball team photo (Box-folder 108-18)
  - CWU Track and Field, team photos, 1940-2000 (Box-folder 109-1)
  - CWU Women's track and field, 1971-1987 (Box-folder 109-2)
  - Cwu Track Coach Art Hutton, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 109-3)
  - CWU Track and field action shots, 1960 (Box-folder 109-4)
  - CWU Cross country, action shots, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 109-5)
  - CWU Track and field action shots, 1960 (Box-folder 109-6)
  - CWU Track and field action shots, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 109-7)
  - CWU Track and field action shots, 1970 (Box-folder 109-8)
  - CWU Track and Field head shots, 1970 (Box-folder 109-9)
  - CWU Track and field, Coach "Spike" Arlt, 1970 (Box-folder 109-10)
  - CWU cross country, action shots, 1975 (Box-folder 109-11)
  - CWU Track and field, 1980 (Box-folder 109-12)
  - CWU track and field action shots, 1980 (Box-folder 109-13)
  - CWU track and field action shots, 1990 (Box-folder 109-14)
  - CWU track and field action shots, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 109-15)
  - CWU track and field action shots, 2001 (Box-folder 109-16)
  - CWU Track and field, team photos (Box-folder 109-17)
  - CWU Football-Team Photo, 1931-1979 (Box-folder 110-1)
  - CWU Football-Team Photo, 1963-1985 (Box-folder 110-2)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 110-3)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1980-1998 (Box-folder 110-4)
  - CWU Football-Team Photo, 1980 (Box-folder 110-5)
  - CWU Football -Team Photos, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 110-6)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1994 (Box-folder 110-7)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1990 (Box-folder 110-8)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 110-9)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1993-2002 (Box-folder 110-10)
  - CWU Football and Women's Soccer, 1995 (Box-folder 110-11)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1995 (Box-folder 110-12)
  - CWU Football- Action Shots, 1995 (Box-folder 110-13)
  - CWU Football and Basketball Action Shots, 1995-2007 (Box-folder 110-14)
  - CWU Football -Team Photos- 1942 football team, 1996 (Box-folder 111-1)
  - CWU Football-Game Photos, 1996-2002 (Box-folder 111-2)
  - CWU Football- Game Photos, 1998 (Box-folder 111-3)
  - CWU Football- Game Photos, 1999 (Box-folder 111-4)
  - CWU Football and Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 111-5)
  - CWU-Action shots, 2002 (Box-folder 111-6)
  - CWU-Action shots, 2002 (Box-folder 111-7)
  - CWU Football-Awards, 2002 (Box-folder 111-8)
  - CWU Football and Basketball, 2002 (Box-folder 111-9)
  - CWU Football- Action shots (Box-folder 111-10)
  - CWU Foootball -Action Shots (Box-folder 111-11)
  - CWU Football-reception (Box-folder 111-12)
  - CWU Football- Crowd shots (Box-folder 111-13)
  - CWU Baseball-Team photos, 1949-1966 (Box-folder 111-14)
  - CWU Baseball-Team photos, 1968-2001 (Box-folder 111-15)
  - CWU Baseball-Action Photos, 1962-1999 (Box-folder 111-16)
  - CWU Baseball- Athletic Directors and Coaches, 1997-2014 (Box-folder 111-17)
  - CWU Volleyball- Team and Action shots, 1979-1990 (Box-folder 112-1)
  - CWU Volleyball- Team photo, 1988 (Box-folder 112-2)
  - CWU Volleyball- Headshots, 1987-1999 (Box-folder 112-3)
  - CWU Volleyball- Team and Action shots, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 112-4)
  - CWU Volleyball- Team and Action shots, 2001 (Box-folder 112-5)
  - CWU Swimming and Diving-Action Shots, Events, 1960 (Box-folder 113-1)
  - CWU Swimming and Diving- Sychronized Swimming, 1960 (Box-folder 113-2)
  - CWU Swimming and Diving - Action shots, Team photos, 1970 (Box-folder 113-3)
  - CWU Swimming and Diving-team Photos, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 113-4)
  - CWU Swimming and Diving - Action shots, Team photos, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 113-5)
  - CWU Wrestling- Action shots, 1966-1991 (Box-folder 114-1)
  - CWU Wrestling-Team Photos, 1966-2000 (Box-folder 114-2)
  - CWU Wrestling -Individual shots, 1966-1991 (Box-folder 114-3)
  - CWU Boxing- Action Shots, 1960 (Box-folder 115-1)
  - CWU Gymnastics, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 115-2)
  - CWU Orchesis, 1960 (Box-folder 115-3)
  - CWU Judo and Karate Clubs, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 115-4)
  - CWU winter sports- skiing, 1960 (Box-folder 115-5)
  - CWU Athletics Hall of Fame, 1962-1996 (Box-folder 115-6)
  - Office Of Testing and Counseling, 1970 (Box-folder 115-7)
  - CWU CHCI Roger Fouts, 1970 (Box-folder 115-8)
  - CWU Field Hockey, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 115-9)
  - CWU Cheerleaders, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 115-10)
  - CWU Golf, 1968-1993 (Box-folder 115-11)
  - CWU Athletic Trainers, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 115-12)
  - CWU Artwork, 1990 (Box-folder 115-13)
  - CWU Campus Buildings, 1990 (Box-folder 115-14)
  - CWU Preview Weekend, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 115-15)
  - CWU Education Students, 1991 (Box-folder 115-16)
  - CWU Faculty, Basketball, 1998 (Box-folder 115-17)
  - CWU Faculty, Basketball, 1999 (Box-folder 115-18)
  - CWU Band, 1999 (Box-folder 115-19)
  - CWU campus Shots, 1999 (Box-folder 115-20)
  - CWU Graduation photos, 2000 (Box-folder 115-21)
  - CWU Students, Sub-Events, 1999 (Box-folder 115-22)
  - CWU Japanese Garden (Box-folder 115-23)
  - Betrayal-Play, 1991 (Box-folder 115-24)
  - Dixie Lee Ray visit to CWU (Box-folder 115-25)
  - CWU Tennis- Action Photos, 1950-1960 (Box-folder 116-1)
  - CWU Tennis- Team Photos, 1949-1993 (Box-folder 116-2)
  - CWU Softball-Action Shots, 1970-2000 (Box-folder 116-3)
  - CWU Softball- Softball Team Photos, 1993-2001 (Box-folder 116-4)
  - CWU Athletics -Miscellaneous, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 116-5)
  - CWU Athletics-Dean Nicholson, 1979 (Box-folder 116-6)
  - CWU Soccer- Women's team, action shots, 1991-1992 (Box-folder 117-1)
  - CWU Soccer- men's team- action shots, team photos, 1986-1993 (Box-folder 117-2)
  - CWU Soccer, 1996 (Box-folder 117-3)
  - CWU Basketball-NAIA Tournament Kansas City tournament, 1984 (Box-folder 118-1)
  - CWU Men's Basketball- Trip to Asia, 1985 (Box-folder 118-2)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 118-3)
  - CWU Men's Basketball- Team Photos, 1990-1999 (Box-folder 118-4)
  - CWU Women's Basketball- Team Photos, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 118-5)
  - CWU Women's Basketball- Action Shots, 1997 (Box-folder 118-6)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-7)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action shots, 1997 (Box-folder 118-8)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-9)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-10)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-11)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-12)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-13)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1997 (Box-folder 118-14)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Photos, 1998 (Box-folder 118-15)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1998 (Box-folder 118-16)
  - CWU Men's Basketball, 1998 (Box-folder 118-17)
  - CWU Basketball-Action Shots, 1960-1970 (Box-folder 119-1)
  - CWU Basketball-Individuals, 1960-1979 (Box-folder 119-2)
  - CWU Basketball- Individuals, 1963-1983 (Box-folder 119-3)
  - CWU Basketball-Action Shots, 1970-1980 (Box-folder 119-4)
  - CWU Basketball- Action Shots, 1980-1990 (Box-folder 119-5)
  - CWU Men's Basketball- Action shots, 1999 (Box-folder 119-6)
  - CWU Men and Women's basketball- Action shots, 2000 (Box-folder 119-7)
  - CWU Women's Basketball- Action Shots, 2001 (Box-folder 119-8)
  - CWU Men's Basketball-Action shots, 2001 (Box-folder 119-9)
  - CWU Event to Honor Dean Nicholson, 2004 (Box-folder 119-10)
  - CWU Basketball-Signs, 2006 (Box-folder 119-11)
  - CWU Men's Basketball-Team photos (Box-folder 119-12)
  - CWU Women's Basketball-Action shots (Box-folder 119-13)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Team photo, 1930 (Box-folder 120-1)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Team photo, 1932-1937 (Box-folder 120-2)
  - CWU Men's basketball-Action Shots, 1977 (Box-folder 120-3)
  - CWU Swimming, Wrestling- Action Shots (Box-folder 120-4)
  - CWU Women's Soccer-Team Photo, 1994 (Box-folder 120-5)
  - CWU Men's Basketball-Team photos, 1995 (Box-folder 120-6)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 121)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 122)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 123)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 124)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 125)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 126)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 127)
  - CWU Athletics-Various headshots, 1998-2000 (Box-folder 128)
  - CWU Basketball Ryan Pepper color negs, 1993 (Box-folder 129-1)
  - CWU Basketball Women's Basketball, 1986-1994 (Box-folder 129-2)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 129-3)
  - CWU Basketball Women's Basketball, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 129-4)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1994-1995 (Box-folder 129-5)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1995-1996 (Box-folder 129-6)
  - CWU Basketball Women's Basketball, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 129-7)
  - CWU Basketball- Team Photos, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 129-8)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 129-9)
  - CWU Basketball Women's Basketball, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 129-10)
  - CWU Basketball Women's Basketball, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 129-11)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 129-12)
  - CWU Basketball- Men's basketball, 1997-2001 (Box-folder 129-13)
  - CWU Faculty Basketball, 1998 (Box-folder 129-14)
  - CWU Basketball- Women's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 129-15)
  - CWU Wrestling-Wrestling Mugs, Headshots, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 130-1)
  - CWU Wrestling Hall of Fame, 1983 (Box-folder 130-2)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1984 (Box-folder 130-3)
  - CWU Wrestling- Head shots, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 130-4)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1985 (Box-folder 130-5)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1987 (Box-folder 130-6)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1988 (Box-folder 130-7)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1989 (Box-folder 130-8)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1990 (Box-folder 130-9)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1991 (Box-folder 130-10)
  - CWU Wrestling- headshots, Action shots, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 130-11)
  - CWU Wrestling- Hall of Fame, 1994 (Box-folder 130-12)